kankaku no
uchigawa wa
sanzan na
amemoyou
shiroi fuku o
nurashinagara
nigeru
you ni kaeru
hitomi wa
hieteiku
iya na mono o
misugita kara
ki ni shinaide,
tsukareta dake
akumu o
miteta dake
aa
heya no naka
rousoku no
yousei wa
teeburu no
ue
kaori dake
nokoshita
kitto
asu no
watashi wa
motto
ima yori
jiyuu to
tobira no
uchigawa de
zutto
negatteru yo
kodoku no
shima no naka
ano hito to
hanashiteru
asu ni nareba
wasureru kara
mou
ki ni shinakute
ii yo
yasashii
koetachi wa
watashi o
sukuwanai
zenbu
wakatteru kedo
soredemo
ii no
ha
garete
itta
miseka
ke no
tekusuchaa
nozoki
komeba
dareka
matteru sa
sotto
hitori
negaeba
tooi
basho kara
yatte
kita
kazetachi ga
utau no
ra
ru
kitto
asu no
anata wa
zutto
ima yori
jiyuu to
tobira no
sotogawa de
sotto
negatteru yo